<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UK Elections App</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login2">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="flip_message">You will now be asked to flip a coin. This is a security measure used to protect against potential malware on your personal computer.

After selecting the result of the coin flip on the voting website, you will be presented with a QR Code. Click “Continue” to scan this.
</string>

    <string name="success_disclaimer">If this vote has been cast against your
will through means such as blackmail,
bribery, intimidation or identity theft,
you may recast you vote.
Click here to find out more

To do this, please bring valid ID  and this
Mobile device to your local polling
Polling station at any point during
the voting period.

You will also be asked to log back in to
your account. Please ensure you know
your credentials.

You ballot ID is:
</string>

    //Web Check Fragment
    <string name="successfull_signin">Signed in Successfully. To continue, please sign into the website"</string>

    //Login Fragment
    <string name="loginBTN">Login</string>
    <string name="passwordHint">Password</string>
    <string name="numberHint">QQ 12 34 56 C</string>

    //Check Terms Fragment
    <string name="check_terms_text">In order to complete your vote, please accept the terms displayed on your Personal Computer.</string>

    //Scanner Fragment
    <string name="manually_enter_QR">Manually Enter</string>
    <string name="testImageView">Manually Enter</string>
    <string name="tryAgainQR">Try Again</string>
    <string name="scannerInstruction">If the aplication is having difficulties scanning the QR, you may try again. Alternativiely, you can manually enter the required values.</string>

    <string-array name="add_num_candidates">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="term">You have signed into the UK voting app. Throughout the proccess, please ensure that</string>
<string name="term1">1) You have casting the vote on your own free will, without manipulation or threats from others.</string>
<string name="term2">2)Your vote is, to the best of your knowledge, private. There is nobody within your environment that knows your vote.</string>
    <string name="term3">3) Throughout the voting process, you will not discussed your voting intentions with another person.</string>


</resources>
